Running out of time. And lives.
Boss Level is a action, science fiction, thriller film directed by Joe Carnahan.
A former special forces agent is trapped in a time loop
and relives his death over and over again.
To escape the terrible situation, he must track
down those responsible and stop them.
Roy Pulver, played by Frank Grillo.
Colonel Clive Ventor, played by Mel Gibson.
Jemma Wells, played by Naomi Watts.
Brett, played by Will Sasso.
Alice, played by Annabelle Wallis.
Dave, played by Sheaun McKinney.
Boss Level is a 2020 American science fiction action film directed by Joe Carnahan and
written by Carnahan, Chris Borey, and Eddie Borey, from a story by the Boreys.
It stars Frank Grillo as a retired special forces soldier who tries to
escape a never-ending time loop that results in his death.
Mel Gibson, Annabelle Wallis, Naomi Watts, and Michelle Yeoh co-star.
Originally announced in 2012 as Continue, it was developed by Carnahan at 20th
Century Fox but did not move forward and sat in development hell.
It was resuscitated in November 2017, with Carnahan, Grillo, Lorenzo di Bonaventura, and Mark
Vahradian producing, and Randall Emmett and George Furla producing and financing.
Filming took place in Georgia from March to May 2018.
It was acquired for theatrical release by Entertainment Studios Motion
Pictures on August 16, 2018, but dropped by the distributor.
The film was eventually released in the United States on
March 5, 2021 direct to streaming on Hulu.
The film explores themes of video game, time loop,
philosophical, satirical, absurd.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.